Tinyiko Maluleke

Tech Officer: Customer Engineer 2

Midrand

+27 12 848 0495

+27 79 120 2090

•

Tinyikor.Maluleke@gmail.com

$\succ\!\!<$

ABOUT -

Experienced Tech Officer: Customer Engineer 2 with strong background in the installation and maintenance of software and hardware. Trained to deliver an exceptional level of customer service in IT support. Ready to take tenplus years in the field to repair, modify, install, and advise in the management of software and hardware.

EDUCATION

NCIT Software DevelopmentUmuzi Academy

Oct 2021 - Current

iiii

> ITIL V4 Foundation

Oct 2019

Secudac

Sept 2019

...

> Cysa+ Torque IT

EXPERIENCE

Tech Officer: Customer Engineer 2

Jul 2009 - Current

Ш̈́

BCX

- Answer and troubleshoot telephonic queries, e-mails, and other media interactions for customers
- Use the provided logging systems to log all calls depending on the type of calls
- Provide help-desk support to end-users of proprietary software
- Configure printer on the network to users
- Do proper troubleshooting to get to the root cause of a customer's problem
- Unlock the accounts and password reset on Active directory
- Remote assistance and remote desktop support
- Installation of software
- Setting up the e-mail accounts
- Good quality of escalations to 2nd level support for resolution

Sep 2006 - Jun 2009



Call Centre Agent

ITA

- Logging calls concerning social Grants & Fraud, Batho Pele Services and SASAMS
- Checking the status of social grant application, that is the application of social grant had been approved or not if not checking the underlying reason
- Handling queries and correspondence
- Resolving customer's complaints
- Dealing with complaints about poor service delivery
- Do 1st line support on SASAMS (Schools Administration and Management System)
- Assign calls to technician on site

Skills











